

ULUGBEK ABDULOEV

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

l am a Web Developer specializing in Front-end Development and UI/UX Design. I have been working professionally in these fields for over 2 years. I'm always curious to create, to improvise and to deliver the best design that fits with what user wants and needs. Very well experienced with HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6, jQuery), Bootstrap and etc, as I have done a decent number of front-end projects using these languages and frameworks. My goal is to produce high quality, good organized and SEO-friendly code.

LANGUAGES

- English
- Russian
- Turkish
- Tajik
- Uzbek
- Persian (conversational)

CONTACTS

- **** +60 18 271 8801
- ulugbekabduloev@gmail.com
- in https://linkedin.com/in/ulugb ek-abduloev-347169ba/
- https://ulugbekdev.github.io/portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CYBERJAYA. MALAYSIA

CENTRE FOR CONTENT CREATION | OCT 2017 - PRESENT

- Develop all user-facing features
- Ensure compatibility across all devices/screen sizes/browsers
- Translate visual and written designs into efficient front end components
- Maintaining and Updating existing websites / student portals
- Fixing bugs

DATA MANAGEMENT

HONG-KONG (PART-TIME REMOTELY)
GOXIP | SEP 2016 - AUG 2019

- Working remotely as a freelancer
- Fixing bugs / Categorizing products

DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR

DUSHANBE, TAJIKISTAN (INTERNSHIP) AUTO 2004 | DEC 2015 - FEB 2016

 Training in designing and implementing database in accordance to end users information needs.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (HONS)IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

LIMKOKWING UNIVERSITY OF CREATIVE TECHNOLOGY CYBERJAYA, MALAYSIA 2014 - 2017

HIGH SCHOOL

TAJIK-TURKISH ECONOMY HIGH SCHOOL DUSHANBE, TAJIKISTAN 2007 - 2012

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SaSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript (ES6)
- iQuery
- ReactJS
- NextJS

- AJAX
- Styled Components
- MongoDB
- Git
- Expression Engine
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe XD

INTERESTS

- Football
- Computer games
- Playing guitar
- Travelling
- Movies
- Music